as a result of the fact that the SVO began the city of
в результате того что началось СВО город
Bakhmut was destroyed so it is
Бахмут уничтожили так
unlikely that it can be
вряд ли наверное он подлежит
restored
восстановлению
what restoration there is simply to
какому восстановлению там просто под
zero everything there that the strike nuclear bombs yes I have not heard
ноль всё там что удар ядерные бомбы да
of such a thing to be honest I am from the city of Khmelnitsky where are you from yes I am from St. Petersburg I understand what you are talking about St. Petersburger put your
понял о чём общаетесь питерец оденьте
mask
маску
back put it on please I am just
назад оденьте пожалуста я просто говорю
talking and put your mask back please please oh that is better what are you
о чём общаетесь
talking about yes it does not matter what I am just talking about what do you
да всё равно о чём просто разговариваю
think why Russia attacked
как считаете почему Россия напала на
Ukraine well a difficult
Украину ну сложный
question it did
вопрос она не напала наверное скорее
not attack probably most likely so it was to restore order probably from that so what is it restoring order there order probably because they offended it it Russia offended offended how it offended shouted there with knives someone there tried and insulted the president of Russia well what is this not tactful somehow not diplomatic I
такое не тактично как-то не дипломатично
understand that that is why you bombed the city of
понял то вы поэтому разбомбили город
Bakhmut no
Бахмут
one was going to bomb
никто не собирался бомбить
anyone if those who
никого если бы там не прятались эти кто
opposed
противостоял
this defense of Ukraine were not hiding there well they
этому защите Украины ну там там
ended up there well they got everything there
оказались ну получили там всё
how old are you
сколько тебе лет
64 how much
64 сколько
64 64
64 64
yeah
угу
what do you work as a
кем работаешь
pensioner pensioner I got it how much is your
пенсионер пенсионер понял сколько у тебя
pension
пенсия
normal pension as it should be that's how it turns out well how much is it
нормальная пенсия как положено так и
supposed to be
получается ну сколько положено
just earned that much and they get how
только заработал столько и получают
much
сколько сколько
in rubles yeah
в рублях да
thirty thirty
тридца тридцатник
thirty super what do you
тридцатник супер
think is it possible to survive in Russia on
как считаешь можно выживать в России на
this money
эти деньги
of course you can I don't I live I
конечно можно я же не Я же живу
live normally I eat everything is fine and
я же живу нормально питаюсь всё хорошо а
what do you eat there pensioners
чем ты питаешься там пенсионеры
eat expired food in Russia I saw
просрочкой питаются в России я видел
why I buy expired food in stores well
почему просрочкой в магазинах покупаю ну
show me that you have something really from the
покажи что у тебя есть что-то реально
store not expired show me the
магазинное не просроченное покажи
products do you have normal products or
продукты нормальные продукты у тебя или
not
нет
yes sausages sausages there show me show me
да сосиски колбаски там покажи покажи
how can I show you well bring it show me
как я тебе могу показать ну принеси
what you really have you're cheating
покажи что реально есть ты обманываешь
pensioners in Russia survive barely eating from the
пенсионеры в России выживают еле-еле с
trash cans what kind of sausages you have
мусорок подъедают какие сосиски у тебя
can be
могут быть
just sold in stores of that topic
просто продаётся в магазинах той то темы
I feed you why do
кормлю что так
n't put it on put it on put it on please put on a mask back
не одень одень одень пожалуйста назад
who told you that please put on a
кто вам такое сказал одень пожалуйста
mask back
маску назад
ok
о'кей
leaks do
просочки питаются
pets eat there well well yes I
там домашние животные ну ну да у меня
also have a dog
тоже собака
great dane well if they give it there then you can
дог вот ну если там дают так можно её и
feed it and let them
скормить и
eat it what do they think
ничего пускай едят они им-то что
I have a normal diet like a
у меня нормальное питание как
regular pensioner's even well of
обычное пенсионерская даже
course I don't go to restaurants well well the
ну конечно я в рестораны не хожу
view is enough for me anyway I
да ну виду-то мне хватает в любом случае
understand
понял
but what do you think about the fact that in Europe
а вот как вы смотрите на то что в Европе
pensioners can go on vacation to the sea
пенсионеры могут ездить отдыхать на море
for example but in Russia no
например а в России нет
one can live as they
кто как хочет так и живёт
want or as they can
кто как хочет или кто как может
and including can yes okay listen but
и в том числе и может да хорошо слушай а
let's do it this way do you think should
вот давай так как ты считаешь должна ли
Russia seize Ukraine
Россия захватить Украину
no of course no no no I don't think should
нет конечно нет нет нет не считаю должна
Russia give Crimea
ли Россия отдать Украине назад Крым
Donetsk
Донецк
Lugansk back to Ukraine I think we need to be friends we need to
Луганск я считаю что надо дружить надо
live peacefully and
мирно жить и
everything and figure it out ourselves and live
всё и разбираться сами по себе и и жить
amicably and calmly well that's how
дружно и спокойно ну вот как как
people are supposed to work well that
положено людям работать ну
's who
вот кто чем
can and what kind of matchmaker hangs over them
может а уж какой там сват над нею там
that's already a different matter for them
висит это уже как-то дело другое им
people it's somehow a matter of indifference what do
людям-то это как-то по барабану
you think who is to blame for
как ты считаешь кто виноват в том что
Russia attacking
Россия напала на
Ukraine  this was the first question but I do
Украину это был вопрос уже первый но я
n't think that it was attacked well who is to
не считаю что напал хорошо кто кто
blame for this war going on
виноват в том что идёт эта война
war no
война
one declared war on anyone
войну вроде никто не объявлял никому
well who is to blame for the
хорошо кто виноват в том что идёт
special operation going on well
спецоперация
Russia wants peace wants people to
ну Россия хочет мира хочет чтобы люди
live normally but it is defending the
жили нормально но она защищает там
Donetsk-Luhansk region there well
Донецко-Луганскую область ну
who is to blame
кто виноват
guilty well probably the presidents
виноватых ну наверное президенты
what presidents Bush Reagan
какие президенты буш Рейган
no probably Putin and Zelyansky probably did
нет наверное Путин с Зелянским наверное
n't share something in the sense Putin is to
что-то не поделили в смысле Путин
blame
виноват
no he is to blame not to blame but I say that
нет он виноват не виноват а я говорю что
since it happened it means that they didn't
раз это получилось значит что-то не
share something between themselves and what did they
поделили там между собой эти а что они
share what did they
поделили
not share
что они не поделили
what should they share at all
что они вообще должны были делить
yes no I'm not saying that to share I'm saying that
да нет я не говорю что делить я говорю
order had to be restored no well you
порядок наводить надо было не ну ты
say that they didn't share something what did
говоришь что они что-то не поделили что
they not share well no no
они не поделили
interest no passion
ну не не интереса не не страстить
interests well here they are with
интересы ну вот
us let's say Putin he is restoring order
они у нас допустим Путин он порядок
and the Ukrainian let's say doesn't want
а украинский допустим не хочет
order once again I didn't understand Russia attacked
порядка ещё раз не понял россия напала
Ukraine because of what
на Украину из-за чего
order should be restored
порядок наводить
what kind of disorder was there
какой а что там за беспорядок был
well if you know
ну если вы знаете
there was a distribution of firearms there
там раздача огнестерного оружия было там
something else there what kind of nuclear
ещё что-то там такое какое ядерное
weapon well tell me in more detail from now on
оружие ну расскажи с этого момента
not nuclear but just a weapon distribution
не ядерного а просто оружие раздача
just jumped on well well well they
просто наскакали ну вот ну вот
humiliated there
унизили там
in short well they
это короче
called everyone all I don't know
ну обозвали там всех всех не знаю
that Russia was humiliated called names
то Россия униженная обозванная
yes before that yes to
да до этого
insult well well in order to offend
да оскорбить ну вот чтобы обидеть
insult well why since Ukraine how
оскорбить ну зачем так как Украина как
Ukraine insulted Russia
Украина оскорбила Россию
well
ну
this Nagilyaku there whoever won't say that
это Нагиляку там это кто не скажет
Putin
тот Путин
this lo there and all that it's
это ло там и всё такое
offensive offensive insulting insulting
это же обидно обидно оскорбительно
no one wanted to call anyone names well
оскорбительно никто же никого обзывать
they wanted to well get it
не хотел ну они захотели ну получайте
how do you think children residents of Bakhmut
как ты дет считаешь жителей Бахмута
which Russia destroyed are they guilty
который уничтожила Россия они виноваты
no of
нет
course not of
конечно нет
course this is called save whoever
конечно это называется спасайте кто
can run wherever you want you want there you
может бегите куда хотите хотите туда
want here
хотите сюда
please if there are military actions there
пожалуйста если там идут боевые действия
something needs to be done people
надо что-то делать надо спасаться людям
need to be saved right well and as for
надо спасаться правильно
wars they fight they
ну а а войны они дерутся они там
fight there they fight there they
сражаются они бьются
bomb there everything
там бомбят там всё
m warriors are warriors well
м вояки есть вояки
and look people in Bakhmut lived and didn't
ну а смотри люди в Бахмуте жили себе не
grieve  Russian speakers did not shout at Nagilyak
тужили русскоязычные не кричали Нагиляку
why they
за что их так
were bombed like that they were bombed for a
разбомбили разбомбили не просто так
reason probably because there was some kind of
наверное потому что там что-то шло
fighting going on there well there are people there well there are
боевое там ну вот люди там
warriors on one side warriors on the other side they are
ну воины с одной стороны воины с другой
hiding well in some
стороны они прячутся ну вот в одних
houses well others are attacking they grandpa look I was
домах ну другие атакуют они дед смотри я
listening to you calmly yes come on now pull yourself together
тебя спокойно слушал да давай теперь
and tell me clearly why you
соберись и скажи мне чётко зачем вы а
can move a little closer because I can't
можешь поближе пододвинуться потому что
hear you well can you move closer to the camera
тебя плохо слышно можешь ближе к камере
let's move a little closer okay yeah
давай ещё чуть-чуть ближе
great so uh tell me tell me why you killed the
супер так э скажи скажи зачем вы убили
residents of Bakhmut
жителей Бахмута
if they were caught in the kill zone then it wasn't
если они попались в зону поражения то не
us who killed them they were caught there what can we
мы их убили они попались туда ну что
do war is
сделать-то война есть
war if a bomb is flying a
война если летит бомба
bomb is flying well here and there as the bomb is
летит бомба ну вот а там как летит бомба
flying wait as the bomb is
подожди как летит бомба
flying as it is flying well from top to bottom
ну как она летит ну сверху ну сверху
like boom and it
вниз так пум вот и
explodes it is aimed at some kind of
взрывается вот она нацелена на какое-то
military well here is an object and the people
видимо военное ну вот объект а люди
are in the
находятся в
kill zone of this bomb they are [ __ ] there
зоне поражения этой бомбы они там ебают
of course it's a pity well
конечно жалко
okay but why throw a bomb where there are
ну хорошо а зачем кидать бомбу там где
people
есть люди
I'm talking about a bomb flying at military facilities there and
я говорю на военные там объекты летит
people are
бомба а люди
nearby then
там неподалёку находятся затем их и
no one kills them and the people what so well
людей никто не убивает что
look the city of Bakhmut was wiped off the face of the
так ну смотри город Бахмут стёрли с лица
earth there
земли
was resistance between the military well yeah yeah
было сопротивление между военными ну что
but it turns out as a result of the fact that the
да да но получается в результате того
SVO began the city of Bakhmut was destroyed
что началось СВО город Бахмут уничтожили
so it's
так вряд
unlikely probably it can be restored
ли наверное он подлежит восстановлению
what kind of restoration there's just
какому восстановлению там просто под
zero everything
ноль всё
and what about the strike of nuclear bombs
а что удар ядерные бомбы
yeah I've never
да
heard of that honestly I'll say
не слышал такого честно скажу
it's when a nuclear bomb explodes there it
это когда ярная бомба взрывается там
destroys everything completely and everything all the buildings
разносит всё напрочь и всё все строение
everything often but it seems
всё подчастую а вроде
like Bakhmut is supposed to be restored
как Бахмут вроде как восстановление
and all the people who
и все которые люди
left there in time they will return to
оттуда вовремя уехали они вернутся к
their restored homes
своим домам восстановленным
grandpa what do you think how many
дед как ты считаешь сколько Россия
houses Russia has restored in your city
восстановила домов в твоём городе
a lot how many what city is yours
много сколько какой у тебя город
Peter Peter in Peter people still live
питер питер в Питере люди живут до сих
without their own apartments a lot of
пор без собственных квартир куча
who
кто
grandpa
дед
no homeless people can live anywhere if
нет бомжи могут жить где угодно если у
they don't have anything don't take it off don't take it off don't
них не хватает ничего не снимай не
take off the mask no  take off
снимай не снимай маску не снимай
yeah
угу
homeless people I know they live well well they are fed they have
бомжи я знаю живут ну ну их кормят у них
flophouses well
ночлежки есть ну
what feed I understand listen but is it
что кормятся я понял слушай а вот это
true that in Russia now they have banned
правда что в России сейчас запретили
singing Soviet songs and people don't know
петь советские песни и люди уже не знают
Soviet songs anymore I
советские песни
don't know please go what do you want do
не знаю пожалуйста пойдте что хотите ты
you remember some Soviet songs still well
ты помнишь какие-то советские песни ещё
probably I remember well can you sing me
ну наверное помню а ну можете мне спеть
some Soviet song
какую-то советскую песню
Soviet yes I
советскую да
can get up
могу вставай страна
huge country get up for mortal combat with the
огромная вставай на смертный бой с
fascist yes what's next yes dark and
фашистской да как там дальше да тёмно и
damn
прокля
hard it was like so what what what is
твёрдой было такое ну и что а что
prohibited what and Katyusha because
запрещено что а а Катюша вот потому что
here in Ukraine it is forbidden to listen to these
у нас в Украине запрещено слушать эти
songs like can you sing Katyusha to me
песни типа можете мне напеть Катюшу
please
пожалуйста
apple trees and
разветали яблони и
pears were scattered fogs floated over the river
груши поплыли туманы над рекой
Katyusha went out to the bank on the high
выходила на берег Катюша на высокий
bank on the steep
берег на крутой
went out further what was there
выходила дальше что там
went out started a song about an eagle
выходила песню заводила про орла
some kind of gray eagle let's talk about the one she
какого-нипного сизового орла давай про
loved the one she loved for
того которого любила которого любила за
that chip she saved oh I understand a  dark-haired girl how dark-
того щепись берегла о понял а смуглянка
haired girl moldovanka sung I also
как смуглянка молдованка поётся тоже
want to remember dark-haired
хочу вспомнить
girl yes now wait there something at
смуглянка да сейчас погоди там что-то на
dawn some morning some
рассвете как-то утром
morning he is
как-то утром он
in the
на
world wait
свете погоди
now in the Near Garden there is a glyanka
сейчас в Ближний сад там глянка
Moldovanka picks
Молдованка собирает
grapes I am redder I am paler
виноград я краснее я бледнее захотелось
suddenly wanted something there well
вдруг чего-то там
now
ну сейчас
how is it
как это
necessary some old people to look there sang samunka I
надо одни старики посмотреть там самунку
I don't remember exactly on the field on the field tanks were
я я точно не помню на поле на поле танки
rumbling you know yes well
грохотали знаете
look into my eyes and go
да а ну посмотрите мне в глаза и спойти
please I love Soviet songs
пожалуйста я люблю советские песни
and what Soviet song do you
а какую советскую песню вы
know well I know of course well on the field
знаете ну знаю конечно ну на поле
there it is from this yes from the film yes yes yes
там это из этого да из фильма да да да
from the
из
film and maybe you know on the border
фильма а может это знаете на границе
clouds are walking gloomy
тучи ходят хмуром
good yes I am on A well come on I remember I I
хорошая да я по А ну давайте я помню я я
can't remember the words but I know
слов не могу вспомнить но я хорошо знаю
this song well yes and the Internationale remember the
эту песни да а Интернационал помните
ringing of the fire but this is not the Internationale it is the
звеите костра а это не интернационал это
pioneers yes there are many songs I say children of the
пионеры да там много песен я говорю дети
fire month at night we are pioneers children of
костра меся ночью мы пионеры дети
workers I remember that so so and what song
рабочих я помню ту так так а какую песню
can you really sing well
которую можете спеть реально
I don't sing  I'm not prepared well I do
ну я же не певёт я же не подготовлен ну
n't have any lyrics I'm Murka Murka
вот у меня текста нет я Мурка Мурка
gopstop
гопстоп
we we came from around the corner yeah yeah yeah can
мы мы подошли из-за угла да дада а
you sing this is a cool song
можете спеть это классная песня
gop-stop we came from around the corner gopstop you
гоп-стоп мы подошли из угла гопстоп ты
took on a lot and now you have to
многое на себя взяла а теперь
pay yeah yeah and so on it's
расплачиваться надо ну ну и так далее
clear and the
понятно
Soviet anthem the Soviet Union anthem we
а гим советского гимн Советского Союза
should remember the
должны помнить
USSR anthem the indestructible union
СССР союз нерушимый
yeah from free publics yeah people
да ис публик свободных да человек
united Great Great Rus' yeah I seemed to be like that
сплотила Великая Великая Русь да я вроде
and what
а чего
okay grandpa look you will support the murder of
ладно дед смотри ты поддержишь убийство
Ukrainians you will
украинцев ты
soon in short
уже скоро короче
you Because you
ты Потому что ты
Why
Почему
I don't even want to watch it anymore it's
я вообще его уже не хочу посмотреть это
just
просто
brutal first such a fool then just
жесть сначала такой дурачок потом просто
some kind of nasty like
какой-то противный
subscribe
лайк подписка
comment subscribe to my Telegram right
комент підпишись на мій Telegram прям
now os vin and
зараз ось він а
popik this is very and very important youtube
попик це дуже и дуже важливо youtube
drives us through the cart into a dark ban and
заганяе нас через каргер в тньовий бан и
very many videos are not shown to people
дуже багато відео не показуется людям
at times not  information about the stream is shown in
вчасно не показуется інформація про
order for us to have a short
стрими тому для того щоб ми мали
operational link to subscribe directly at
оперативный зв'язок підпишиться прямо
once and there is a pop there in the telegram okmdeo, there is
зараз а попик там в телеграмі окмдео ще
also useful and relevant information and we are
теж цікава и корисна інформація и мы
responsible for you to trim the permanent
повинні з вами тримати постійний
operational link regardless of the view  I'll
оперативный зв'язок незалежно від того
show you about it YouTube Glory to
чи покаже вам про це YouTube слава
Ukraine subscribe
Україні підпишись